Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO Records 1989.0080
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Ruth Warren Greenberg, undated, 1940-1961
  - Subseries C: Education and Information [CSLC, AFL-CIO], undated, 1946-1961
    - Connecticut
      - Labor's League for Political Education (LLPE), 1953-1956 (Box 11:, Folder 603-605)
        - Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 11:, Folder 607)
      - Council for the Advancement of Economic Education, 1953-1961 (Box 11:, Folder 608-614)
      - State of, 1955 (Box 12:, Folder 615)
        - Department of Education, 1958 (Box 12:, Folder 616)
        - Labor Council, 1957-1959 (Box 12:, Folder 617-622)
      - Citizens for Public Schools, 1955, 1958 (Box 12:, Folder 623-624)
    - “Economic Education in the Schools”, 1961 (Box 12:, Folder 625)
    - Executive Council, 1954-1957 (Box 12:, Folder 626)
    - “F”, 1955 (Box 12:, Folder 627)
    - Federations of Teachers, 1950-1959 (Box 12:, Folder 628-630)
    - Films and filmstrips, 1954-1955 (Box 12:, Folder 631)
    - “G”, 1954-1955 (Box 12:, Folder 632)
    - Greenberg, Ruth Warren, 1954-1959 (Box 12:, Folder 633)
    - “H”, 1955 (Box 12:, Folder 634)
    - Hartford Labor Council, undated, 1959 (Box 12:, Folder 635)
    - Industrial Union Council, 1951-1956 (Box 12:, Folder 636)
    - “K”, 1958 (Box 12:, Folder 637)
    - Labor Education Legislation, 1959 (Box 12:, Folder 638)
    - Labor education programs, 1958 (Box 12:, Folder 639)
    - Labor Management Institute (UConn), 1959 (Box 12:, Folder 640)
    - Library Project, 1956 (Box 12:, Folder 641)
    - Machinists, International Association of, 1955 (Box 12:, Folder 642)
    - McDevitt, James L., 1955-1957 (Box 12:, Folder 643)
    - Mental Health Association Educational Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 12:, Folder 644)
    - Murray, Esther, 1956-1957 (Box 12:, Folder 645)
    - “N”, 1958-1959 (Box 12:, Folder 646)
    - National Labor Service, 1959 (Box 12:, Folder 647)
    - New Haven Central Labor Union/Council, 1957 (Box 12:, Folder 648)
    - New Haven Community Health Center, 1957 (Box 12:, Folder 649)
    - New Haven Council on Economic Education, Greater, 1959 (Box 12:, Folder 650)
    - Play: “A Land Beyond the River”, 1957 (Box 12:, Folder 651)
    - Political leaflets, 1956, 1958 (Box 12:, Folder 652)
    - Prisons and prison industry, 1957-1958 (Box 12:, Folder 653)
    - Research materials, 1946-1957 (Box 12:, Folder 654-659)
      - Congressional scorecards, undated (Box 12:, Folder 660)
      - House voting records, undated (Box 12:, Folder 661)
      - Individual records, undated (Box 12:, Folder 662)
      - Political Action Committee Bulletins, undated (Box 12:, Folder 663)
    - “S”, 1957 (Box 13:, Folder 664)
    - Scholarships, 1959 (Box 13:, Folder 665)
    - School materials program, 1956-1970 (Box 13:, Folder 666-686)
    - Shakespeare Project, 1957 (Box 13:, Folder 687)
    - Silvey, Ted F., 1957 (Box 13:, Folder 688)
    - Stamford Central Labor Union, 1955-1956 (Box 13:, Folder 689)
    - Stamford Education Program, 1956-1958 (Box 13:, Folder 690-691)
    - State legislature, 1955-1956 (Box 13:, Folder 692-693)
    - State legislature bills, 1955 (Box 13:, Folder 694)
    - Stay in School Campaign, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 695)
    - “U”, 1959 (Box 13:, Folder 696)
    - Union label, 1954-1955 (Box 13:, Folder 697)
    - United Packinghouse Workers, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 698)
    - Votes—flood control, 1940-1955 (Box 13:, Folder 699)
    - “W”, 1956 (Box 13:, Folder 700)
    - Welfare Commission, 1961-1963 (Box 13:, Folder 701-712)
    - Willimantic Labor Council, 1959 (Box 13:, Folder 713)
  - Subseries D: Educational Conferences, undated, 1954-1961
    - Conferences—general, 1954-1955 (Box 14:, Folder 714)
    - Bridgeport Conference on School Drop-Outs, 1961 (Box 14:, Folder 715)
    - Bristol Women's Meeting, 1957 (Box 14:, Folder 716)
    - Conference on Economics, 1957 (Box 14:, Folder 717-718)
      - Correspondence (Box 14:, Folder 719)
      - Photograph (Box 14:, Folder 720)
    - Conference on Merger, 1957 (Box 14:, Folder 721)
    - Connecticut Conference on Education, 1954-1955 (Box 14:, Folder 722)
    - Federation of Teachers Conference, 1957-1958 (Box 14:, Folder 723)
    - International Affairs Conference, 1958 (Box 14:, Folder 724)
    - International Trade Conference, 1958 (Box 14:, Folder 725)
    - Labor Education Conference, 1956-1958 (Box 14:, Folder 726)
      - Photograph, undated (Box 14:, Folder 727)
    - Labor Management Institute, UConn, 1957-1958 (Box 14:, Folder 728-729)
      - Photograph (Box 14:, Folder 730)
    - Legislative Conferences, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 731-733)
      - Correspondence (Box 14:, Folder 734)
      - Fact sheet (Box 14:, Folder 735)
      - Legislative Conference for Women, 1957 (Box 14:, Folder 736-738)
      - Correspondence (Box 14:, Folder 739)
      - Minutes (Box 14:, Folder 740)
      - Registration (Box 14:, Folder 741)
    - National Institute for Labor Education, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 742)
    - National Institutes on Rehabilitation and Labor Health Services, 1959, 1961 (Box 14:, Folder 743)
    - Schulman Conference, Harry, 1958 (Box 14:, Folder 744)
    - Union Representatives Conference, Full-time, 1958 (Box 14:, Folder 745)
    - Voter Registration Workshop, 1957-1958 (Box 14:, Folder 746)
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1958 (Box 14:, Folder 747)
    - White House Conference on Education, 1955 (Box 14:, Folder 748)
    - Women's Conference, 1958 (Box 14:, Folder 749-751)
      - Correspondence (Box 14:, Folder 752)
      - Registration packets (Box 14:, Folder 753)
    - Governor's Commission to Study Child Labor Laws, undated (Box 14:, Folder 754)
- Series III: John J. Driscoll, undated, 1952-1986
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1953-1972
    - Section 1—Individuals, 1957-1972
      - Bailey, John N., 1961-1966 (Box 15:, Folder 755)
      - Barber, John, 1964 (Box 15:, Folder 756)
      - Bazan, George, 1967 (Box 15:, Folder 757)
      - Cotter, R., 1967 (Box 15:, Folder 758)
      - Dallas, Donald, 1972-1973 (Box 15:, Folder 759)
      - Dempsey, John D. (Governor), 1964-1967 (Box 15:, Folder 760)
      - Dodd, Thomas J., 1958-1967 (Box 15:, Folder 761)
      - Driscoll, Margaret Conners, 1957-1959 (Box 15:, Folder 762)
      - Giaimo, Robert, 1957-1967 (Box 15:, Folder 763)
      - Glynn, John, 1965 (Box 15:, Folder 764)
      - Osborne, Jack, 1965-1966 (Box 15:, Folder 765)
      - Perry, Herbert, 1963-1964 (Box 15:, Folder 766)
      - Ribicoff, Abraham A., 1957-1968 (Box 15:, Folder 767)
      - Smith, Wilbur, 1965-1966 (Box 15:, Folder 768)
      - Sandahl, Eric, 1964 (Box 15:, Folder 769)
      - Thomas, William, 1964-1967 (Box 15:, Folder 770)
      - White, Jack, 1965 (Box 15:, Folder 771)
    - Section 2—CSLC Officers, 1953-1968
      - Bober, Joseph, 1967 (Box 15:, Folder 772)
      - Driscoll, John J., 1953-1968 (Box 15:, Folder 773-775)
      - Kershner, Leonard, 1961-1968 (Box 15:, Folder 776)
      - Matchko, Madeline, 1966-1968 (Box 15:, Folder 777)
      - Zolot, Norman, 1963-1968 (Box 15:, Folder 778)
  - Subseries B: Convention Materials, undated, 1961-1967
    - 4th Constitutional Convention, 1961 (Box 15:, Folder 779-782)
    - Legislative, Political and Educational Convention, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 783-784)
    - 5th Constitutional Convention, 1963 (Box 15:, Folder 785-787)
    - Legislative, Political and Educational Convention, 1964 (Box 15:, Folder 788-789)
    - 6th Constitutional Convention, 1965 (Box 15:, Folder 790-797)
    - Legislative, Political and Educational Convention, 1966 (Box 15:, Folder 798-808)
    - 7th Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 16:, Folder 809-815)
    - Annual summer school (Box 138:, Folder 3858)
    - Anti-Injunction Law, 1967 (Box 16)
    - Area redevelopment, 1959-1962 (Box 16:, Folder 817)
    - Auto insurance rates, 1967 (Box 16:, Folder 818)
    - Bus drivers, 1966 (Box 16:, Folder 819)
    - Community Services Conference, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3867)
    - Convention kit, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3870)
    - Convention material, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3874-3875)
    - Conventions and other meetings, undated (Box 139:, Folder 3859)
    - Conventions and other meetings, undated (Box 139:, Folder 3860)
    - Conventions, undated (Box 139:, Folder 3861)
    - COPE, undated (Box 138:, Folder 3856)
    - COPE Committee, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3876-3877)
    - COPE meeting, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3864)
    - Election campaign letters, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3878)
    - Energy Transportation Act, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3872)
    - Fair Tax Committee meetings, undated (Box 138:, Folder 3857)
    - General subject file, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3865)
    - Latino Trade Unionists, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3869)
    - Legislative bulletins, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3866)
    - People for Ribicoff reception, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3868)
    - Political meetings (June 10th), undated (Box 140:, Folder 3863)
    - Resolutions, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3873)
    - Special meeting, undated (Box 140:, Folder 3871)
    - Summer school, undated (Box 139:, Folder 3862)
  - Subseries C: Political and Legislative File, 1958-1972
    - Collective Bargaining
      - Hospital Employees, 1964-1965 (Box 16:, Folder 820)
      - Municipalities, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 821)
    - Compensation for crime victims, 1966 (Box 16:, Folder 822)
    - Community Health Center Plan—New Haven, 1964-1968 (Box 16:, Folder 823-829)
    - Connecticut Constitutional Convention, 1965 (Box 16:, Folder 830)
    - Connecticut Consumer Association, 1965-1968 (Box 16:, Folder 831-833)
    - Connecticut Insurance Industry, 1972 (Box 16:, Folder 834)
    - Connecticut “65”, 1964 (Box 16:, Folder 835)
    - Dickey-Lincoln School Hydro Project, 1965-1968 (Box 16:, Folder 836-838)
    - Disadvantaged children, 1965 (Box 16:, Folder 839)
    - Drug and pharmacy bills, 1965 (Box 16:, Folder 840)
    - Fair Labor standards, 1960-1967 (Box 16:, Folder 841)
    - Farm Labor, Public Act 78, 1962 (Box 16:, Folder 842)
    - Federal aid to education, 1965 (Box 16:, Folder 843)
    - Legislative data, 1965 (Box 16:, Folder 844)
    - Legislative data, 1967 (Box 16:, Folder 845)
    - Legislation, labor, 1969 (Box 16:, Folder 846)
    - Lie detector material, 1964-1965 (Box 16:, Folder 847)
    - Little Davis Bacon Act, 1971 (Box 16:, Folder 848)
    - Long Island Bridge data, 1963-1968 (Box 16:, Folder 849)
    - Manpower Development and Training Act, 1963-1968 (Box 16:, Folder 850)
    - Massachusetts Transportation Bill, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 851-852)
    - Medicare, 1963-1966 (Box 17:, Folder 853)
    - New Haven Railroad, 1962-1967 (Box 17:, Folder 854-858)
    - Occupational Health and Safety Bill, HR 14816, 1968 (Box 17:, Folder 859)
    - Personal income tax, 1948-1967 (Box 17:, Folder 860-861)
    - Pollution, general, 1964-1967 (Box 17:, Folder 862)
      - Air pollution, 1967 (Box 17:, Folder 863)
      - Air pollution by motor vehicle, 1966-1967 (Box 17:, Folder 864)
      - Water pollution, 1963 (Box 17:, Folder 865)
    - Quality Stabilization Bill, 1963 (Box 17:, Folder 866)
    - Radiation Control Act Bill 1181, 1961-1966 (Box 17:, Folder 867-868)
    - Re-appointment and re-districting, 1964-1965 (Box 17:, Folder 869)
    - Right-to-work data, 1961-1966 (Box 17:, Folder 870)
    - Short work week, 1962 (Box 17:, Folder 871)
    - Social security, 1965-1967 (Box 17:, Folder 872-873)
    - State budget, 1961-1963 (Box 17:, Folder 874)
    - State income tax data, 1963-1966 (Box 17:, Folder 875)
    - State Technical Services Act, 1965 (Box 17:, Folder 876)
    - Strike breaking, 1961-1965 (Box 17:, Folder 877)
    - Sunday and holiday closings, 1961-1962 (Box 17:, Folder 878)
    - Taxes, 1965-1966 (Box 17:, Folder 879)
    - Test Ban Treaty, 1962-1963 (Box 17:, Folder 880)
    - Tuition tax credit, 1964-1967 (Box 17:, Folder 881)
    - Unemployment compensation, 1960-1964 (Box 17:, Folder 882-883)
    - Urban affairs, 1962-1965 (Box 17:, Folder 884)
    - U.S. Congress, 1967 (Box 17:, Folder 885)
    - Workmen's compensation, 1959-1960 (Box 17:, Folder 886-887)
  - Subseries D: Committee on Political Education [COPE], undated, 1959-1968
    - AFL-CIO Platform proposals and analysis, 1964 (Box 18:, Folder 888)
    - Bridgeport, 1966-1967 (Box 18:, Folder 889-890)
    - Contributions, 1958-1966 (Box 18:, Folder 891-893)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 18:, Folder 894)
    - Platform proposals and analysis, 1964 (Box 18:, Folder 895-897)
    - Conclusions, 1964 (Box 18:, Folder 898)
    - Democratic party DAFA, 1966 (Box 18:, Folder 899)
    - Democratic platform, 1966 (Box 18:, Folder 900)
    - Election results, 1966 (Box 18:, Folder 901)
    - Federal candidates, 1966 (Box 18:, Folder 902)
    - State candidates, 1966 (Box 18:, Folder 903)
    - Voter registration, 1966 (Box 18:, Folder 904)
    - Voter registration fund, 1962 (Box 18:, Folder 905)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1968 (Box 18:, Folder 906)
    - Democratic Party data, 1961-1966 (Box 18:, Folder 907)
    - Democratic Party leaders, CT, 1964-1967 (Box 18:, Folder 908)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960-1966 (Box 18:, Folder 909)
    - Presidential campaign, 1968 (Box 18:, Folder 910)
    - Republicans, 1959-1964 (Box 18:, Folder 911-912)
    - Republican Labor League, 1964-1967 (Box 18:, Folder 913-914)
    - Scholarship Fund— Thomas W. Cooke Scholarship, undated (Box 18:, Folder 915)
    - West Virginia primary, 1960 (Box 18:, Folder 916)
  - Subseries E: Connecticut State Departments, 1957-1968
    - Commission for Higher Education
      - Accreditation and Licensing Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 18:, Folder 917-922)
      - Accreditation and Licensing Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 19:, Folder 923-924)
      - Budget Committee, 1966-1969 (Box 19:, Folder 925-926)
      - Community Colleges, 1965-1967 (Box 19:, Folder 927-931)
      - Committee on Teacher Education, 1967 (Box 19:, Folder 932)
      - Student Financial Assistance Committee, 1966 (Box 19:, Folder 933)
      - Foundation for Financial Assistance, 1966-1967 (Box 19:, Folder 934)
      - Fiscal Policy Committee, 1968 (Box 19:, Folder 935-936)
      - Interim Education Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 19:, Folder 937)
      - Legislation, 1965-1967 (Box 19:, Folder 938-939)
      - Program Planning Commission, 1966 (Box 19:, Folder 940)
      - State Scholarship Commission, 1963-1968 (Box 19:, Folder 941)
      - Scholarship Subcommittee, 1966 (Box 19:, Folder 942)
      - Teacher Education/Training Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 19:, Folder 943)
        - Correspondence, undated (Box 19:, Folder 944)
        - W.G. Hill, Director, 1967-1968 (Box 19:, Folder 945)
        - D.H. McGannon, 1965-1968 (Box 19:, Folder 946)
        - Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 19:, Folder 947-949)
        - Salary data, 1966-1969 (Box 19:, Folder 950)
        - Statutes—Commission for Higher Ed., 1965-1967 (Box 19:, Folder 951)
        - Studies creating Commission, 1960-1965 (Box 19:, Folder 952)
        - Study: “Higher Education Enrollment”, 1967 (Box 19:, Folder 953)
        - Study: “Teacher Education in CT”, 1967 (Box 19:, Folder 954)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1965-1968 (Box 20:, Folder 955-962)
    - Fiscal Study Commission, 1957 (Box 20:, Folder 963)
    - Health, Department of, 1963-1967 (Box 20:, Folder 964)
    - Insurance, Department of, 1966 (Box 20:, Folder 965)
    - Labor, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 20:, Folder 966-967)
    - Research Advisory Committee, 1965 (Box 20:, Folder 968)
    - State Board of Mediation and Arbitration
      - Activity reports and hearing schedules, 1964-1968 (Box 20:, Folder 969)
      - Alternates, 1961-1967 (Box 20:, Folder 970)
      - Annual reports, 1959-1967 (Box 20:, Folder 971)
      - Fact finders, 1966-1968 (Box 20:, Folder 972-975)
      - General correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 20:, Folder 976-977)
      - Hearings, 1964-1968 (Box 20:, Folder 978-979)
      - Key decisions, 1965 (Box 20:, Folder 980)
      - Mediator applications, 1962-1963 (Box 20:, Folder 981)
      - Minutes, 1965-1968 (Box 20:, Folder 982)
      - Policy manuals, 1967 (Box 20:, Folder 983)
      - Procedures and election rules, 1964-1965 (Box 20:, Folder 984)
      - Salary Schedules, 1965-1967 (Box 20:, Folder 985)
    - Cases
      - Arrow Hart ☀ Hegeman strike, 1967 (Box 20:, Folder 986)
      - Bridgeport Brass, 1965 (Box 20:, Folder 987-988)
      - Bridgeport Gas Company, 1965 (Box 20:, Folder 989)
      - Brunswick-Union, Inc., 1962-1965 (Box 20:, Folder 990)
      - Connecticut Railway and Light, 1963 (Box 20:, Folder 991)
      - Fafnir Bearing, 1962, 1967 (Box 20:, Folder 992-993)
      - Mitchell Dairy, 1963 (Box 20:, Folder 994)
      - Royal-U.A.W. dispute, 1965 (Box 20:, Folder 995)
      - Singer-Local 227 I.U.E., 1964 (Box 20:, Folder 996)
      - Skinner Precision Industries, 1962 (Box 20:, Folder 997)
      - Terry Steam Turbine, 1962 (Box 20:, Folder 998)
      - United Illuminating Company, 1966 (Box 21:, Folder 999)
      - Veeder Root, 1963 (Box 21:, Folder 1000)
      - Wichester Western-Olin Matheson, 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 1001)
    - State Board of Mediation and Arbitration, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1002)
    - Stutz, Robert L., Chairman SBMA, 1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1003)
    - State Development Commission, 1963 (Box 21:, Folder 1004)
    - Research Advisory Committee, 1965 (Box 21:, Folder 1005)
  - Subseries F: Affiliated Unions, undated, 1957-1968
    - Amalgamated Transit Workers, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1006)
    - Building Service Employees International Union, 1964-1965 (Box 21:, Folder 1007-1009)
    - Machinist strike—Vickers, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1010)
    - Police and Fire Unions, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1011-1012)
    - Police Unions, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1013)
    - Postal clerks, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1014)
    - Teachers
      - American Federation of, 1957-1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1015-1016)
      - Connecticut Federation of, 1963-1966 (Box 21:, Folder 1017-1018)
      - Waterbury Federation of, 1965 (Box 21:, Folder 1019)
  - Subseries G: Councils, 1959-1968
    - Labor Councils, Greater
      - Bridgeport, 1961-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1020)
      - Bristol, 1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1021)
      - Hartford, 1959-1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1022)
      - Meriden, 1965-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1023)
      - Naugatuck, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1024)
      - New Britain, 1962-1966 (Box 21:, Folder 1025)
      - New Haven, 1962-1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1026)
      - New London Central, 1963 (Box 21:, Folder 1027)
      - Norwalk, 1962-1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1028)
      - Stamford, 1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1029)
      - Torrington, 1963,1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1030)
      - Waterbury, 1959-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1031)
      - Willimantic Central, 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 1032)
    - Local Central Labor Bodies, 1962, 1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1033)
    - Building and Construction Trades Council, 1957-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1034-1035)
    - New England AFL-CIO Council, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1036-1045)
      - By-laws, 1960 (Box 21:, Folder 1046)
      - Financial, 1960-1965 (Box 21:, Folder 1047)
      - General Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1048)
      - Minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 21:, Folder 1049)
      - Meetings, 1962-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1050)
      - M-14 Rifle, 1960 (Box 21:, Folder 1051)
      - Unemployment data, 1960, 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 1052)
  - Subseries H: AFL-CIO, undated, 1953-1968
    - Biemiller, Andrew J.—Director, Legislation, 1953-1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1053)
    - Bookstaver, Alexander—Director, Investment, 1964-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1054)
    - Coyle, Francis J.—Community Service Liaison, 1963-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1055)
    - Davis, Walter—Director, Education, 1966-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1056)
    - Dudley, Tilford E.—Director, Speaker's Bureau, 1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1057)
    - Goldfinger, Nathaniel—Director, Research, 1964-1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1058)
    - Kirkland, Lane—Assistant to President, 1966 (Box 21:, Folder 1059)
    - Meany, George—President, 1964, 1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1060)
    - Mills, Paul—Public Relations, 1962 (Box 21:, Folder 1061)
    - Murray, Esther—Director, Women's Auxiliary, 1964, 1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1062)
    - Rothman, Julius—Anti-poverty programs, 1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1063)
    - Rourke, J.M.—Deputy Chair, COPE, 1961-1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1064)
    - Schnitzer, W.E.—Secretary-Treasurer, 1961 (Box 21:, Folder 1065)
    - Seidman, Bert—Director, Social Security, 1967-1968 (Box 21:, Folder 1066)
    - Stanley, Miles—Assistant to President, 1966 (Box 21:, Folder 1067)
    - Taylor, George—Economist, Research, 1965-1966 (Box 21:, Folder 1068)
    - Thompson, Hugh—Director, Region I, 1964 (Box 21:, Folder 1069)
      - Central Labor Bodies AFL-CIO, undated (Box 21:, Folder 1070)
      - Advisory Committee on State and Local Central Bodies, 1965 (Box 21:, Folder 1071)
    - Annual reports, 1961-1962 (Box 21:, Folder 1072)
    - Conferences, 1962, 1964 (Box 21:, Folder 1073)
    - General Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1074)
    - Proposed constitutions, 1966 (Box 21:, Folder 1075)
    - Dues structure, 1962-1966 (Box 21:, Folder 1076)
    - Wage and hour enforcement, 1967 (Box 21:, Folder 1077)
    - Unorganized clippings, periodicals, correspondence, fliers, ephemera, notes, financial records, administrative records, 1950s-1980s (Box 209)
      General note
      [Subjects include: Industrial Aircraft Lodge, Connecticut, The Congressional Special.]
  - Subseries I: Committees and Commissions, undated, 1961-1972
    - Blue Ribbon Commission, undated (Box 136)
      - Connecticut Governors Task Force, undated (Box 136:, Folder 3850)
      - Higher education and the economy of Connecticut, undated (Box 136:, Folder 3851)
      - Higher education: hearings and background, undated (Box 136:, Folder 3852)
      - Urban problems, undated (Box 136:, Folder 3853)
      - Waterbury, undated (Box 136:, Folder 3854)
    - Citizen's Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 22:, Folder 1078)
    - Consumer Interest, President's Commission on, 1966-1967 (Box 22:, Folder 1079)
    - Connecticut Council/National Council on
      - Crime and Delinquency, 1965-1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1080)
      - General, 1965-1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1081)
      - By-laws, 1965-1967 (Box 22:, Folder 1082)
      - Committee reports, 1966-1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1083)
      - Legislative, 1967 (Box 22:, Folder 1084)
      - Judge Mead dinner, 1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1085)
      - Membership manual, undated (Box 22:, Folder 1086)
      - Minutes, 1965-1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1087)
      - Newsletter, 1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1088)
    - COPE, endorsed questionnaires and responses, undated (Box 137:, Folder 3855)
    - Council of Economic Advisors, undated (Box 135:, Folder 3847)
    - Economic Education, Connecticut Council on, 1966-1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1089)
    - Economic Education, Joint Council on, 1966-1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1090)
    - General Assembly, Connecticut Citizens Commission, 1966 (Box 22:, Folder 1091)
    - Government Agencies, Committee on, undated (Box 22:, Folder 1092)
    - Human Relations, Connecticut Council on, 1964-1967 (Box 22:, Folder 1093)
    - Human Relations, Archbishop O'Brien Commission, 1965-1967 (Box 22:, Folder 1094)
    - Human Rights, Commission on, 1961, 1965 (Box 22:, Folder 1095)
    - Human Rights, Steering Committee, 1965 (Box 22:, Folder 1096)
    - Intergovernmental Relations, Advisory Council, 1970-1972 (Box 22:, Folder 1097)
    - Letters to the Editor, undated (Box 135:, Folder 3846)
    - Northeast Regional Manpower, 1965-1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1098-1105)
    - Second Regional Plan, 1963-1968 (Box 22:, Folder 1106-1109)
    - ULA operations, undated (Box 135:, Folder 3848)
    - Urban Coalition, 1965-1967 (Box 22:, Folder 1110)